(Sheldon:)I distinctly ordered the Leonard Nimoy
Mr. Spock cardboard standee.
(Sheldon:)Why would I feel safer with
Zachary Quinto at the foot of my bed?
(Penny:)I don't know.
He was pretty badass on Heroes.
(Sheldon:)You're right. I'll give him a shot.
(Penny:)Hang on.
- Penny, you have plans for dinner?
- You guys going somewhere?
(Leonard:)No, I mean just you and me.
(Amy:)Ooh.
(Penny:)Have you thought this through?
(Leonard:)Yes. And I think we should go anyway.
(Sheldon:)No, can't do it.
Sorry, Quinto, you're going back.
(Amy:)If you and Leonard get back together,
Sheldon and I will finally have...
(Amy:)- ...someone to go on double dates with.
- What about me and Howard?
(Amy:)Fine, we can double with you too.
(Amy:)So insecure.
(Bernadette:)Where are you guys going to eat?
(Bernadette:)Penny?
(Minister:)Do you, Penny, take Leonard
to be your lawful wedded husband?
(Penny(turning, heavily pregnant):)Well, it's a little late for me
to start saying "no," isn't it?
(Bernadette:)Penny?
Sorry. I just remembered
I've got to stop by the drugstore.